Danny, this is a wonderful meal.
Danny, 晚餐太棒了!
Please come and live with me.
你来和我一块儿住吧.
Do you think he does this all the time?
你以为他每天都这样吗?
Lisa, you see how we live.
Lisa, 我们的生活状况你是清楚的.
Ask Hannah if she wants to sink to our level.
你问问Hannah她是不是也想沦落成我们这样.
This is unusually civilized.
这顿饭的确是异乎寻常的好.
It's not often I make my sauce.
我平时可不经常做调味酱.
I want to know if this is your mother's sauce.
我想知道这和你妈妈做的调味酱是不是一样的.
The basic recipe is the same,
做法基本上一样,
but I put in a few things my mother would not approve of.
只是我还加了一些我妈妈不会同意放的东西.
I broke a couple of the rules.
我打破了几条常规.
Your mother has rules about spaghetti sauce?
你妈妈做意大利面的调味酱也有规矩吗?
Of course!
当然有啦!
My mother's rules are about clothes.
我妈妈的规矩是关于衣服的.
Like what?
比如说?
Like skirt length. No minis.
比如说裙子的长度. 不许我穿迷你裙.
Bummer.
没劲.
In high school she'd always ask me if I intended to leave the house that way.
我读中学的时候, 她老是问我是不是打算就这样穿着迷你裙出门.
She must have been surprised the first time you came home from college.
那你第一次从大学回家时她肯定大吃一惊.
Oh yes.
Oh 是的.
My parents sure were.
我爸妈还不是一样.
My dad has one rule: be practical.
我爸爸这个人有一条原则: 人得实际一点儿.
And I had changed my major from business to theater arts. Oh well.
可是我把专业从商业改成了戏剧. Oh 我的天.
Besides, Danny, you're using that theatrical stuff in your job now.
可不管怎么说, Danny,你现在这份工作正好要用上戏剧专业的知识.
Oh yeah, it's always a show down at the copy place.
Oh 是的, 复印社里总要发生一些戏剧性的事件.
How's your film coming, Michael?
你那部电影怎么样了, Michael?
Are you breaking any rules?
你也要打破常规吗?
I don't think so.
我想不会.
My advisor asked me who my major influence has been.
我的指导老师问谁对我的影响最大.
I told him it changes every week.
我告诉他说每个星期都不一样.
I haven't even found the rules yet.
我还没有发现什么常规呢.
Well, you'll know what to do when you find them.
Well, 等你发现了, 你就知道该怎么干了.
Break'em!
打破常规!